Carrie Chambers

USER EXPERIENCE ANALYST

(865) 209-6924 cfrazier1314@hotmail.com carriechambers.github.io

Know your user. Let me help! My passion is understanding user needs in order to provide the best user experience possible. I offer you my unique blend of analytics and creativity to provide UX solutions that benefit your users and your business.

EXPERIENCE

Dell Technologies, Nashville TN — Fulfillment Advisor

IANUARY 2016 - PRESENT

- Maximize the use of data to make informed, strategic decisions that ensures customer satisfaction and fulfillment success
- Develop cross-functional relationships in order to align business goals and ensure on-time and accurate order fulfillment for our customers.
- Key member of the enablement team that launched Dell's third fulfillment center in North America

Haslam College of Business, Knoxville TN — Website Management Assistant SEPTEMBER 2012 - SEPTEMBER 2015

- Assisted in web page creation and updates using HTML and CSS
- Maintained up-to-date social media posts using Wordpress and Hootsuite
- Trained new users to use Adobe Dreamweaver and Contribute HTML, CSS, Adobe

Georgia-Pacific, Atlanta GA — Demand Planning Intern

IUNE 2014 - DECEMBER 2014

Collaborated with marketing and manufacturing to create an aligned forecast for GP Professional Wiper line using IDA software

EDUCATION

Nashville Software School, Nashville TN — UI & UX for Digital Product Design SEPTEMBER 2018 - DECEMBER 2018

- 14-week workshop covering Digital Product Design and UX principles
- Topics covered: HTML, CSS, user research & insights, user personas, journey maps, usability, accessibility, wireframes, prototypes, and more
- Included capstone project to incorporate lessons learned to real-world application
 - o I researched competitors, conducted user interviews, created user personas and journey maps, defined the problem, generated wireframes, oversaw user tests, completed a prototype, and presented my findings to the class

University of Tennessee, Knoxville TN — B.S. Supply Chain Management

AUGUST 2012 - DECEMBER 2015

- International Business concentration
- Cumulative GPA: 3.76/4.00

SKILLS

Concepts

Data analysis & insights

Cross-functional communication

User research

User interviews

Usability testing

Journey mapping

Paper to high-fi prototyping

Design systems

Time management

Quick learner

Presentations

Tools

Tableau

Power BI

Sketch

Invision

HTMI

CSS

Access

INTERESTS

Traveling

Camping

Hiking

Financial health

Crafting